

Nida Muna Fadhilla

Frontend Developer

munanida@gmail.com

0895617842143

Magelang, Indonesia

linkedin.com/in/nidamuna in

instagram.com/nidafadhilla_

I am a graduate of a bachelor's degree in Information Technology with work experience as a frontend developer. I have experience building user-friendly and responsive user interfaces using React.js, Tailwind CSS, and JavaScript. I am enthusiastic about continuing to learn and acquiring new skills in web development. I am used to working in a goaloriented team with excellent communication skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Staff

Perpustakaan Universitas Muhammadiyah Magelang

09/2021 - 07/2022

-Task

- Responsible for conducting checks and updating the operating system and applications.
- Perform checks on supporting devices and regularly back up all data in the library.
- Responsible for the existing system and network.
- Redesign the library's website and manage its content.

Frontend Developer

Hayuning Indotech

07/2022 - 05/2023

- Responsible for developing user interfaces on websites using React.js, Tailwind CSS, and Web3.
- Worked closely with the backend team, design team, DBA. DevOps team, and project manager to complete a project

Supporting Staff Programmer

Dinas Komunikasi dan Informatika Kab. Magelang

06/2023 - Sekarang

-Task

- Responsible for making information systems and services in the form of websites with Codelgniter
- Making a full-stack website in accordance with official needs in Magelang Regency

EDUCATION

Teknik Informatika

Universitas Muhammadiyah Magelang

09/2018 - 02/2022

3.94

LANGUAGE

Indonesia Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

SKILLS

CSS Html

React.is

PHP & MySQL Python

Codelaniter

Elementor

Wordpress

Next.is

PROJECT

Home Learning Indonesia (Agu 2022 - Des 2022)

- Creating a landing page for https://hli.co.id/
- Creating frontend of Home Learning Indonesia for three needs: staff, teacher,
- Using the Javascript, ReactJS, and Tailwind CSS programming languages

Jataka (Sep 2022 - Okt 2022)

- Creating a landing page for https://jataka.io
- Using the Javascript, ReactJS, and Tailwind CSS programming languages

Meta Visi Nusantara (Jan 2023 - Feb 2023)

- Creating a landing page for https://metavisinusantara.com/
- Make content for MVN using the Javascript, ReactJS, and Tailwind CSS programming languages

Digismart (Feb 2023 - Mar 2023)

- Creating several displays from https://marketplace.digiswap.finance/
- Using the Javascript, NextJS, and AntDesign programming languages

Indo Circular Waste (Apr 2023 - Jun 2023)

- Create landingpage and admin dashboard interface from https://www.indocircularwaste.co.id/
- Using the Javascript, ReactJs, and AntDesign programming languages

PUBLICATION

Program Komputer Sistem Pakar Kesesuaian Lahan Salak Dengan Prolog dan Metode Forward Chaining Surat Pencatatan Hak Cipta (Haki) / Apr 2022

The Influence of Blockchain Implementation for Virtual Meetings at Home Learning Indonesia

iJET Vol. 18 No. 06 (2023) / Mar 2023

CERTIFICATION

Certification Completeness: Front-End Development

freeCodeCamp.org (12/2022)

CCNAV7: Introducing to Networks

Cisco Networking Academy (02/2022)

Sertifikat Kompetensi: Software Development

BNSP (06/2021)